Guide to the Craig Wirth broadcast journalism audio-visual collection 1903-1990s, bulk 1950s-1990s
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- 2002 addendum
  - (Box 51)
    - Set point, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1417)
    - Dive, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1418-1420)
    - Turkey, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1421)
    - Sagewood, Otto's babies, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1422-1424)
    - Cloud rim, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1425-1427)
    - Old airplane, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1428)
    - Computer set, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1429)
  - (Box 52)
    - Air 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1430)
    - University of Utah basketball 66-67, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1431)
    - England?, 1990 February; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1432)
    - Guard 2 of 5, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1433)
    - Don't waste Utah, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1434)
    - Historic television photos, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1435)
    - Fruit stands, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1436)
    - Chew, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1437)
    - Wirth match, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1438)
    - New close 211, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1439)
    - Don't waste 769, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1440)
    - Mill 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1441)
    - Adventure convention, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1442)
    - Miller tape, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1443)
    - Internet production, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1444)
    - Drive-in new audio, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1445)
    - 6B Wirth, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1446)
    - Don Laughlin 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1447)
    - Sots, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1448)
    - Senile seashells, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1449)
    - Ogden theater 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1450)
    - Mill Road tour 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1451)
    - Great Salt Lake, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1452)
    - West High Ti kwon do, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1453-1454)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1455-1456)
    - Clix, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1457)
    - Cap, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1458-1460)
    - World War II pilot, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1461)
    - Halloween, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1462)
    - Tubing, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1463)
    - Santa; health, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1464)
    - Tom Nassalki interview, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1465)
    - Camp Kostopulos 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1466)
    - Logan theater, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1467-1468)
    - Ogden food, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1469)
    - Organ, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1470-1471)
    - Barbershop, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1472)
    - Baseball cover, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1473)
    - Artificial heart, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1474)
    - Highlight 2-26, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1475)
    - Power 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1476)
    - Wirth, 1999 March; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1477)
    - Electricity in Utah, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1478)
    - 25th Street 5, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1479)
    - Weather, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1480)
    - Lionel 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1481)
    - Larry Miller 11, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1482)
    - Ballet standup, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1483)
    - Iceberg, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1484)
    - Lincoln 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1485)
    - Train 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1486)
    - Globes, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1487)
    - Basketball, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1488)
  - (Box 53)
    - Cooking class, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1489)
    - Ron Boone interview, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1490)
    - William Christensen interview, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1491)
    - Ogden theater, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1492-1494)
    - Camp Kostopulos, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1495)
    - Morrisville A, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1496)
    - Halloween 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1497)
    - Car collector; Trax; music, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1498)
    - Bees; suicide; old mill historical pictures, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1499)
    - 4-H, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1500)
    - Organ, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1501-1502)
    - Power 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1503)
    - Wheller Halloween, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1504)
    - 25th, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1505-1506)
    - 4-H kid, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1507)
    - Clix, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1508)
    - Wirth 2000, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1509)
    - Food stand, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1510)
    - Dance, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1511-1512)
    - Organ Phantom of the Opera, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1513)
    - Don't waste 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1514)
    - Helper 11, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1515)
    - Old mill, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1516)
    - Packard, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1517)
    - Kearns, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1518)
    - Old Pine 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1519)
    - Train 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1520)
    - Road tour - Capital Theatre, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1521)
    - Book pictures, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1522)
    - Trax, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1523)
    - Halloween B-roll, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1524)
    - ROTC 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1525)
    - Nutcracker, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1526)
    - Pic poet, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1527)
    - Wirth 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1528)
    - BH 2-91, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1529)
    - Helper 10; old Hotel Utah, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1530)
    - Studio camera - photo, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1531)
    - Weather, November 06; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1532)
    - Wright and art, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1533)
    - Engineers monitor in stall, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1534)
    - Skywest, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1535)
    - Set lighting, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1536)
    - Micro - touch up, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1537)
    - Set micro, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1538)
    - ARBXS, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1539)
    - Good set details, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1540)
    - Chris's call, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1541)
    - Set pictures from Mac, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1542)
    - Set going up, X2 coming down, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1543)
    - Details set - red rock details, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1544)
    - Set rehearsal, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1545)
    - McDemats stuff, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1546)
    - Open set, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1547)
    - Unidentified videocassette, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1548)
    - Unidentified videocassettes, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1549-1550)
    - Phantom of the Opera special, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1551)
  - (Box 54)
    - 150 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1552)
    - 401 seniors on centennial interviews, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1553)
    - Ballet West film transfer, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1554)
    - Access - final parts all assembled, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1555)
    - KTTV news footage, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1556)
    - Clips, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1557)
    - Evans and Sutherland, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1558)
    - Simulation takes flight, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1559)
    - New business reel (commercials), 1999; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1560)
    - Evans and Sutherland coporate overveiw, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1561)
    - Airplane, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1562)
    - Unidentified videocassette, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1563)
    - 50th Anniversary Craig Wirth special: basketball; parade, 1998; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1564-1569)
    - Science and Technology Center in Computer Graphics and Scientific Visualization, 1991 March; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1570)
    - Aurore Electronics - computer asset recovery, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1571)
    - Kruse International, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1572)
  - (Box 55)
    - Wirth 3D, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1573)
    - Pharmaceutical 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1574)
    - Capitol 6, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1575)
    - Craig Wirth demo, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1576)
    - Jonathan's juggling 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1577)
    - Old twinkies, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1578)
    - Sears 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1579)
    - B-17 and B-24 bombers, Europe, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1580)
    - Wirth graphics, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1581)
    - Salt Lake Olympic Winter Games B-roll, 1999 May; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1582)
    - Protest, January 04; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1583)
    - National air cargo, 1998 July 24; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1584)
    - Twinkies dub, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1585)
    - Dragging the bow, undate; Audiocassette (Cassette 1586)
    - 1960s, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1587)
    - Dr. Parmley, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1588)
    - 1960s treat, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1589)
    - Jennifer Kraus, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1590)
    - 944 (Utah 56), undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1591)
    - RC Willey, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1592)
    - Golden Twinkies Award, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1593)
    - Craig Wirth, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1594)
    - Dog obedience tape 2 of 2, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1595)
    - Howie's series, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1596)
    - Clouds of Doubt, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1597)
    - Logger tape, 1999 November 14; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1598)
    - Logger tape, 1999 January 18; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1599)
    - D-Day: Air Force story, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1600)
    - Village that met them again, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1601)
  - (Box 56)
    - Bungalo 1, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1602)
    - Logger tape, 1998 October 28; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1603)
    - Logger tape, 1998 November 18; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1604)
    - Logger tape, 1998 November 12; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1605)
    - Logger tape, 1998 November 17; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1606)
    - Logger tape, 1998 January 19; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1607)
    - Ride: real spirit of Sturgis, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1608)
    - University of Southern California minority business development program, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1609)
    - Kids dance card, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1610)
    - Satellite dish, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1611)
    - First 3 spex, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1612)
    - Newspaper, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1613)
    - Scott Dittrich films: action sports, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1614)
    - Pain - wrestling, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1615)
    - God; tennis, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1616)
    - 501 Levis; Nike, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1617)
    - Travel 3, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1618)
    - A Grateful Nation Remembers, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1619)
    - Dupre, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1620)
    - Antigone, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1621)
    - Lipton Benny 3, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1622)
    - University of Utah basketball highlights, 1960-1961; 1965-1966; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1623)
    - SNC Wirth finale, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1624)
    - Education - don't drop out, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1625)
    - Ogden's capert commercials 1, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1626)
    - Conter's spotted asses, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1627)
    - Captain Dyn., undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1628)
    - 50th anniversary Wirth special - for Utah, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1629-1630)
    - Craig Wirth VWG special, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1631)
    - Centennial photo compilation I, 1995 April 10-August 02; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1632)
    - Centennial photo compilation II, 1995 August 03-September 26; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1633)
    - Centennial photo compilation III, 1995 September 27-November 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1634)
    - Centennial photo compilation IV, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1635)
    - Centennial photo compilation V, 1996 January 02-February 21; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1636)
    - Great centennial road tour volume 1, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1637-1641)
    - Salt Lake City Fire Department - emergency vehicle operations, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1642)
    - Unidentified videocassettes, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1643-1644)
    - Motor trend, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1645)
    - Trolley Square - Linda Ormes, undated; 2-inch videotape (Reel 1646)
    - Utah Transit Authorities (UTA) vacation sensations, undated; 2-inch videotape (Reel 1647)
  - (Box 57)
    - RC Willey, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1648)
    - Huntsman Cancer Institute interiors and exteriors B-roll, 1999 Fall; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1649)
    - 5 (coat), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1650)
    - Unidentified videocassettes 20-22, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1651-1652)
    - Unidentified videocassette 30, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1653)
    - Unidentified videocassette, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1654)
    - 703 - Ogden's carpet commercials, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1655)
    - 713 - Mountain Pacific Thursday, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1656)
    - Tape 5 commercials, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1657)
    - 215 - Oil to burn; down town; 1960s, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1658)
  - (Box 58)
    - News set 1-4, undated; Hi-8 videocassette (Cassette 1659-1662)
    - News set 5, 1995 December 05; Hi-8 videocassette (Cassette 1663)
    - News set 6-22, undated; Hi-8 videocassette (Cassette 1664-1679)
    - Nikki Stone 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1680)
    - Knights and warriors 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1681)
    - Internet 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1682)
    - Craig Wirth special, 1998 June 19; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1683)
    - Airport stuff, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1684)
    - Christmas tree auction, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1685)
    - 25 continued, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1686)
    - Wine 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1687)
    - School 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1688)
    - Antelope Island, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1689)
    - Union Station, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1690)
    - Toys, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1691)
    - Footprints 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1692)
    - McDonald's field trip, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1693)
    - Disneyland - Mickey Mouse's birthday, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1694)
    - Sound storm 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1695)
    - Hat 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1696)
    - WJLA Washington DC: Van fire, 1988; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1697)
    - Jumper? 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1698)
    - Helicopter, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1699-1700)
    - Salt Palace; Plum Alley, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1701)
    - Plum 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1702)
    - Plum Trax, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1703)
    - Plum 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1704)
    - Wheeler Farm, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1705-1706)
    - This is the Place, 1997 August 06; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1707)
    - This is the Place 5, 1997; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1708)
    - Tap 4 tots, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1709)
    - Salt Palace; worthless dogmeat scum, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1710)
    - Jim Dandy 5, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1711)
    - Thanksgiving 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1712)
    - Wheeler Farm upper, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1713)
    - Post Utes, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1714)
    - Arnie 1944, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1715-1716)
    - Fence 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1717)
    - Tree Utah 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1718)
    - Eaton basketball, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1719)
    - Slot cars 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1720)
    - Drug store 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1721)
    - Grethe Peterson, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1722)
    - Great Salt Lake, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1723)
    - RC Willey, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1724)
  - (Box 59)
    - Peace Gardens, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1725-1726)
    - Organ, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1727)
    - Bungalows, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1728)
    - Operation Rescue protest, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1729)
    - Bungalows track, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1730)
    - Queen, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1731)
    - Fence 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1732)
    - Lotus 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1733)
    - Edit use only, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1734)
    - Smoke stack, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1735)
    - Wirth audio, June 16; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1736)
    - Rose Parade, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1737)
    - Store 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1738)
    - Drug store 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1739)
    - Soccer, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1740)
    - Smoke stack song, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1741)
    - Max Payne 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1742)
    - La Prille, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1743)
    - America's Choice, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1744)
      Promotional video suggesting Utah as host for the Olympic Winter Games
    - Present day 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1745)
    - Kid space 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1746)
    - Bike man 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1747)
    - Toys, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1748-1749)
    - Snow and kids, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1750)
    - State Street, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1751)
    - Triplets, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1752)
    - Dinosaurs of the Dial, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1753)
    - Kids space 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1754)
    - Wirth bowl 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1755)
    - Rex the pig 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1756)
    - Nutcracker, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1757)
    - Ribs 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1758)
    - Tree Utah, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1759)
    - Slot cars 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1760)
    - Square dance, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1761-1762)
    - Question 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1763)
    - Pet resort 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1764)
    - Gay clubs, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1765)
    - CNBC audio, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1766)
    - Bird show, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1767)
    - Wirth bowl 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1768)
    - Slot cars 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1769)
    - Sundance, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1770)
    - Pool special, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1771)
    - Race car, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1772)
    - Library, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1773)
    - Wirth TV 9, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1774)
    - Mom 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1775)
    - Hotels 1-2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1776)
    - Train, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1777)
    - Model trains, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1778)
    - Lagoon, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1779-1780)
    - Clarion 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1781)
    - Train, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1782)
    - Burger King, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1783)
    - Old mill, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1784)
    - Kearns, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1785)
    - Kevin Band, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1786)
    - Wirth Mom's Café, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1787)
  - (Box 60)
    - Craig Wirth does Sundance, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1788-1789)
    - Mormon Meteor, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1790-1791)
    - Clarion pictures, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1792)
    - Lagoon 1-4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1793-1796)
    - Train 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1797)
    - Lambs Canyon, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1798)
    - B-17 bomber, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1799)
    - Wirth match, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1800)
    - Lincoln, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1801-1803)
    - Don Laughling 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1804)
    - Wirth golf, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1805)
    - July 4th, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1806)
    - Jimsair Aviation Services, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1807)
    - Max, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1808)
    - Horse Wwisperer, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1809-1810)
    - Road tour salt harvest, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1811)
    - Mary's Vale, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1812)
    - Moms 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1813)